Guide to the Roy M. Huffington Oil Company Records, 1977-2006 MS 575
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Roy M. Huffington Oil Company Records
1958-2008
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Huffington, Roy M.
MS 575
81 Linear Feet (71 boxes)
8.43 Gigabytes Nearline access: MS0575aip_001 (8.43 GB)
This collection documents the business history of the Roy M. Huffington, Inc., also known as Huffco. There are photos, correspondence files, videos, as well as awards and speeches that Roy M. Huffington gave while he served as CEO and president of the company.
Biographical / Historical
Roy M. Huffington, geologist, oilman, philanthropist, and U.S. ambassador, was born Oct. 4, 1917, in Tomball, Texas. His father was also an oilman but died in an accident when Roy was 16. Enrolling at Southern Methodist University, Roy earned a geology degree in three-and-a-half years and then went on to Harvard, where he graduated with a masters and a doctorate in geology. From 1942 to 1945 he served in the U.S. Navy as first ensign and then lieutenant commander. Returning to Texas after the war, he worked as a field geologist for Humble Oil (now a part of ExxonMobil) until 1956, when Huffington struck out on his own. Eventually Roy M. Huffington, Inc. was established into an oil and gas exploration company. He had saved enough money to cover expenses for three years, and for the first 18 months he did not make "a red cent," he said. Then, however, he hit oil in 17 of the first 18 wells he drilled.
Huffington's company, subsequently known as Huffco, grew to be a major independent international oil company active around the world. Observing that the geology of Indonesia seemed to resemble that of the Gulf Coast, Huffington suspected that oil or natural gas might be found there. Thus, in 1966 Huffco signed a production sharing contract with Pertamina to explore in the Kutai Basin of the Mahakam River delta in East Kalimantan, Indonesia. The initial exploration objective was oil, but in 1972 Huffco discovered a giant natural gas reserve at Badak Field. Huffco and Pertamina collaborated to build a liquefied natural gas plant in Bontang, and the first shipping took place in 1977.
Subsequently Huffco joined forces with Mobil Oil Indonesia to expand the size of the Indonesia natural gas project. After seven years of this field's operation, Indonesia became the world's largest liquid natural gas supplier. In 1989 Huffington sold his business to the Chinese Petroleum Corporation of Taiwan.
In 1990 Huffington accepted appointment by President George H. W. Bush to be ambassador to Austria. He served in that post for three years, working to improve business ties with the former Soviet bloc. After his ambassadorship, he returned to Houston and resumed his position as chairman of the board and chief executive officer of Roy M. Huffington, Inc., the independent international oil company that remained after the sale of Huffco to the Chinese.
While serving as ambassador to Austria he joined the board of the Salzburg Global Seminar, an international policy center, and in 1994, he was elected its chairman, a position which he held until 2007. Huffington also served as the chairman of the Asia Society, a New York-based charity, for seven years in the 1980s. His philanthropic activities were wide ranging, related especially to education and medicine. To cite a few examples, he founded the Huffington Foundation, a Houston-based charity, and he and his wife, the former Phyllis Gough, who died in 2003, established the Huffington Center on Aging at Baylor College of Medicine. Having been a member of the Alpha Tau Omega fraternity at Southern Methodist University, he made a significant donation to the Alpha Tau Omega Educational Foundation, which provides scholarships for undergraduate members of the fraternity.
On July 11, 2008, while vacationing in Italy, Huffington died in Venice of natural causes. He was 90.
Scope and Contents
This collection documents the business history of the Roy M. Huffington, Inc., also known as Huffco. There are photos, correspondence files, videos, as well as awards and speeches that Roy M. Huffington gave while he served as CEO and president of the company. Most of the information highlights the Badak liquified natural gas plant, founded by Huffco Inc. in early 1972. Series I: Indonesia joint venture, Badak, and LNG includes photos and correspondence files detailing the establishment of the Badak plant. Subcommittee minutes include committee, the LNG expansion coordinating committee, and the exploration subcommittee. Series II: Audio-Visual showcases in photographs, audio, and video Roy Huffington as business man, friend, and colleague. Some of the files deal with: work anniversaries, professional photographs, and plant construction and design. Series III: LNG projects captures locations and projects that Huffco was interested in and or involved with. This series is mainly text files. Series IV:Correspondence is composed of correspondence that was discussed between the company and other entities/ parties. The correspondence files that are particularly interesting are the ones on Interferon Foundation. This Foundation was one that dealt with a trial drug on cancer. Series V:Addendum is rich in photographs. There are photos of Roy M. Huffington and some significant dignitaries including: George W. Bush senior and Colin Powell. In late 2019 additional collecting and processing produced an additional four series. In 2020 and 2021 a final round of collecting and processing produced a final addendum of materials largely focusing on research materials and highlighting RMHI's domestic start in the United States.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research with the exception of items restricted by the Donor and the Woodson Research Center because dissemination of their content may constitute a clearly unwarranted invasion of personal privacy or a libel of a living person, or because content relates to the personal, family, and confidential business affairs of the Donor or other persons referenced in the Records. Specific timeframes or other conditions for removal of restrictions will be negotiated on a case-by-case basis.
Stored offsite at the Library Service Center and require 24-hour notice for retrieval. Please contact the Woodson Research Center at 713-348-2586 or woodson@rice.edu for more information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection was a gift donated by Michael Huffington, Terry Huffington, and the Huffington Foundation, Terry Huffington and Ralph Dittman, Trustees, on February 22, 2013.
Related Materials
Please refer to Roy M. Huffington Personal and Professional papers,1972-2009, MS 688; Roy M. Huffington Naval Papers, 1942-2005 MS 611 for more information on the Navy and Mr. Huffington; Roy M. Huffington Ambassadorial Papers, 1988-2008 MS 617; as well as the Huffington and allied families' papers, 1650-1955 MS 883.
Index Terms
Subjects
Oil and gas; Liquefied natural gas industry; Offshore oil industry; Community activists; Petroleum industry and trade
Document Types
business records
Places
Indonesia; Kalimantan (Indonesia)
- Series I: Indonesia joint venture, Badak, and LNG, 1969-1981
  - Accounting and tax subcommittee meeting minutes (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Allied Chemical Corporation Union Texas petroleum division (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Allied Chemical Corporation Union Texas petroleum division, 1977-02-09-1978-11-14 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Ultramar, 1969-02-04-1980-12-15 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - American Ultramar limited, 1975-01-21-1978-11-16 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Austral Petroleum Gas Corporation, 1969-05-19-1979-12-19 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - P.T. ASA case (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
  - C.V. Nastra concern v. Roy M. Huffington Inc., 1979-07-13 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Department of the Army U.S. Army topographic command (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Operations audit report, 1978-05-24 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Audit report file non-operator, 1977-08-22-1980-08-01 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Ascope, 1977-08-26-1978-09-01 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - P.T. Badak 100th LNG cargo from Bontang celebration, 1979-07-24 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Badak cash flow, 1977-04-27-1977-05-20 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Badak condensate loading and storage facilities, 1975-11-05 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Badak gas facility, 1976-10-06 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Badak OCEF relending agreement (unofficial), 1977-04-19 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Badak crude oil entitlement procedure, 1980-08-04 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Badak LNG expansion project progress reports, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - LNG expansion project financing (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Badak LNG plant sales, 1979-11-26 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Badak sale of crude to oasis, 1980-09-02 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Badak field increased deliverability and Bontang plant capacity (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Bontang plant expansion trains 5 and 6, 1979-01-16 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - LNG transportation from Indonesia to Japan-Leif Hoegn co. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Badak trustee and paying agent agreement and Badak escrow agreement (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Articles of association on the Badak Natural Gas Liquefaction Company (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Badak LNG expansion project (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Badak LNG expansion project progress report (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Badak LNG expansion project train no. 5 future (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Badak LNG expansion project position papers for trains 3 and 4 at same time (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Badak LNG project additional trains (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Badak LNG expansion project progress report (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Badak LNG expansion project development plan, 1978-11 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Gas production for Bontang LNG plant and fertilizer plant after expansion to four, 1979-06-25 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Sales contract Columbia LNG corporation (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Badak overrun financing (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Badak trust agreement (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Badak utilization negotiations summary (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Balikpapan booklet (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bechtel Incorporated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Bontang LNG Plant expansion project in Pertamina and Bechtel letter of intent (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Borden project (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Indonesian Borobudur restoration contribution (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Badak LNG project freight rates for t/a, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Burmah gas transport freight rate, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Transportation agreement and Pertamina and Burmah gas transport limited (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Burmah Oil Company, Ltd., Burmah oil tankers, Ltd., Burmast East Shipping Corporation and Pertamina (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Cattle (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Centre for strategic and international studies (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Wallace R. Clark, Jr. vs. Roy M. Huffington Inc. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Indonesia clippings (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Indonesia clippings (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Coal prospecting rights in Indonesia (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Condensate system (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Crude oil lifting agreements between Pertamina and ILAPO (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Crude oil marketing in Indonesia (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Crude oil production and sales, Badak field, and East Kalimantan, Indonesia (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Crude oil sales from East Kalimantan proposed structure (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - General correspondence Indonesia (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence- Singapore office (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Indonesia Joint Venture correspondence (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - D.K.K.A.- Pertamina (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - D.K.K.A organization chart telephone guide and administrative correspondence procedure (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - D.K.K.A/ Pertamina monthly meeting (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - DKKA Letter no. 5718/75 proposed training of employees abroad (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Pacific - Indonesia LNG company (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Drilling and production status (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - East Kalimantan economic evaluation (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - End users participants (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Department of energy federal governmental policy on liquefied natural gas (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Engineering subcommittee meeting minutes (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Engineering subcommittee meeting minutes (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Esso chemical company- now Exxon- project reviews (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Executive club members (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Expatriate policy guide (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Job classification schedule (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Expatriate policy guide (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - P.T. Badak Natural Gas Liquefaction Company, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence Jakarta office (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Expatriate premiums (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Exploration subcommittee meeting minutes (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Exploration reports (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Facilities expansion project operations, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Fertilizer plant (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Film (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Financial statements Indonesia Joint Venture (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Foreign capital investment in Indonesia (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Foreign exploration non-association (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Foreign oil companies in Jakarta (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - FPC approval of LNG imports (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - First National City bank primary signers (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Foreign tax credit problems Indonesian production sharing contract (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Gas project subcommittee meeting minutes (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - General Dynamics Quincy shipyard (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Golden Eagle Indonesia Limited (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Gunung Bakaran housing project (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Gunung Bakaran Huffco office (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Charles L. Hicks correspondence, etc. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Home ownership plan (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Huffco East Asia Inc. (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Huffco warehouse and crating company proposal (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Inca, LTD.- Anabas island South China sea production sharing contract area (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Indonesia - Japan LNG project (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Indonesia contract negotiations (Box 3, Folder 25,26)
  - Indonesian income tax laws applicable to corporation (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Indonesian marketing (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Indonesian Petroleum Association (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Indonesian - Union Oil Company of California and Attaka field (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Internal revenue service regulations (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Insurance subcommittee meetings (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Jakarta Hilton executive club (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Joint coordinating committee meeting (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Joint operating agreement Nilam oil and gas unit East Kalimantan (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Joint management group (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - LNG file (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - LNG economics revised (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - LNG expansion project progress report (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - LNG expansion coordinating committee (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - LNG plant (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - LNG plant liquids (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Additional LNG sales documents to be supplied from Badak and Arun projects (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Dome LNG project for export to Chubu and other Japanese buyers (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Floating LNG plant proposal (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - LNG project (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - LNG project negotiations (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - LNG services agreement Pertamina and RMHI (Huffco) group (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - LNG joint coordination meetings (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - LNG project financing (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - LNG project insurance meetings (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Liquefied natural gas decision and order denying petition spot sales (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Liquefied natural gas sales contract Pertamina and Columbia LNG corporation spot sales to East Coast (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - LNG Shipping (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - LNG shipboard personnel training program (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - LNG surplus (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - LNG transportation agreement (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - LNG sales contract committee (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Spot sales agreements to U.S. East coast (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Liquefied natural gas sales contract between Pertamina and Boston Gas Company (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Management reports Indonesian joint venture (Box 4, Folder 16,17,18,19)
  - Manning charts, job description, and salaries (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Indonesia- R.I. methanol in Indonesia Thysse group (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Minister of Mines Department (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Mitsubishi Corporation (Box 4, Folder 23,24)
  - Mitsubishi International Corporation (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Mitsubishi Petroleum Development Company., LTD. (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Mobil/Arun LNG project (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Mobil's tax ruling (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Monthly activity report (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Names of people with various companies (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Nilam oil and gas unit agreement (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Nippon Bear Oil Company LTD. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Nissho- IWAI Co., LTD (Box 5, Folder 4,5)
  - Oil development project Badak field (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Organization chart foreign personnel (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Office of Foreign Direct Investments - U.S. Department of Commerce (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Joint venture operating committee budget (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Joint venture operating committee budget, general, and administrative and overhead (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Operating committee minutes, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Operating committee meeting minutes, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Operating committee and subcommittee - name changes to receive copies of minutes, etc. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Operating group report on Badak LNG project (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Osaka, Japan branch establishment (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Overhead correspondence (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Overseas schools advisory council (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Overriding royalty (Box 6, Folder 1,2,3)
  - Personnel in Indonesia expatriates and nationals (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Pacific resources, Inc. Honolulu, Hawaii (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Payout status report (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Management committee file (Box 6, Folder 7,8)
  - Acturial certificate for the plan and taxable year, 1977-12-31 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Proposal for executive tax services (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Roy M. Huffington, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Management committee file no.1 (Box 6, Folder 12,13)
  - Management committee file no.1 (corporate policy and procedures manual) (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Management committee no.1 (analysis of investment facilities), 1977-06 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Personnel - overseas (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Personnel - expatriates and families (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Personnel policy guide expatriates (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Personnel reports (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Pertamina- cabinet ministers- personnel and BKKA personnel (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Pertamina and BKKA Organization charts, 1976-05-06 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Pertamina - Japan Indonesia LNG Loan agreement (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Pertamina - other companies amended production sharing contract on crude oil payments (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Pertamina public relations policies (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Pertamina - additional request of acreage (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Pertamina general correspondence (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Bechtel and Pertamina LNG plant and related facilities agreement (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Pertamina Badak LNG project (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Pertamina - Japan Indonesia LNG Co., LTD. Badak LNG plant (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Policy committee - Indonesian Joint Venture group (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Sanga sanga area in East Kalimantan (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Production sharing contract amendent (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Pertamina - Mobil Oil Indonesia Inc. - agreement on principles of plant lease and processing arrangements (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - P.S.C renegotiation's meeting with president Suharto, 1977-01-15 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Production facilities (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Monthly production summary - East Kalimantan (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Production sharing contract agreement (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Production sharing contract agreement, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - PSC release of approximately 6,138 sq. kilometers of sanga sanga in East Kalimantan (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Operating agreement Nilam unit- (total) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Pertamina - Huffco agreement and amendment to production sharing contract crude oil proceeds (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Production sharing contract- renegotiation- between Pertamina and Roy M Huffington Inc. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Bidding on new land, Southeast Sumatra (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - RMH production sharing agreement between Perusahaan Negara Tambang Batubara and Shell Mijnbouw N.V. (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Ranger building systems (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Reception list of Indonesia guests (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Seller's sales contract pricing package for Badak LNG expansion project (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Santan Terminal (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Securities and exchange commission (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - General Soeharto's message (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Santan Terminal facilities joint operating agreement (Pertamina, union and japex- attaka unit, Huffco- Badak (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Skyline Building (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Sumatra program (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - The Superior Oil Company- formerly Austral Petroleum Gas Corporation (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Structure of entity to operate, or own, and operate Indonesian liquefaction plant (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Talks (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Talks - his excellency the president of the republic of Indonesia Soeharta (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Indonesian tax decree method of computation, payments of corporate tax, interests, dividends, and royalty tax (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Tax calculation for production sharing contractors for Indonesian income taxes (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Tax equalization calculations (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Technical services agreement (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Tankers (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Training of Indonesians and expatriate Indonesia personnel managers required by DKKA (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Union oil company of California joint operating agreement - Tuju unit East Kalimantan (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Utilization of foreign workers (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Unitization project (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Work permits and visas regulations (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Work program and budget, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - "The world as it is" advertisement in publication of issue on Indonesia (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Worldwide Pertamina Foundation (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Badak Field Oil Development project, 1973-01 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Banglico - board of directors- P.T. Badak Natural Gas Liquefaction Company (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Banglico - board of directors, Badak (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Banglico - board of directors- P.T. Badak Natural Gas Liquefaction Company (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Badak shareholder meeting and proposals (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Badak board of directors meetings (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - P.T. Badak Natural Gas Liquefaction Company balance sheet (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - PT Badak permanent community "Guest" house Bontang, Kalimantan (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - P.T. Badak - natural gas plant organization- Bontang (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Shareholder agreement- Badak (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Producers' audit of P.T. Badak Natural Gas Liquefaction Company operator of the Bontang LNG plant (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Dedication of LNG plant and facilities (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Terms by Pertamina for Badak LNG plant engineering and construction (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Insurance - Badak (Bontang) LNG plant (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - LNG meetings - Osaka (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Badak gas sales negotiations (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Processing agreement and agreement for exclusive use and operation of plant - Pertamina and joint venture (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Badak LNG brochure distribution (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Badak LNG plant cost estimate and schedule (Box 8, Folder 19)